Dorothy Thompson Papers
Dorothy Thompson Papers
- Family papers
  - Sinclair Lewis
    - Sinclair Lewis manuscripts
      - "It Can't Happen Here", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 49)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", original typescript; 1 item (Box 49)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 49)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", original typescript; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", (novel) pp. 1-100 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", pp. 101-200 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", pp. 201-300 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", pp. 301-400 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "It Can't Happen Here", pp. 401-498 typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "Prodigal Parents" Chapter I, revised version; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "Self Portrait" Article, original typescript; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "Snob Ads", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "The Story that Mack McMack Told", original typescript; 1 item (Box 50)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", (play) original typescript; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", original typescript; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", original revised copy; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", original revised copy; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings", original revised copy; 1 item (Box 51)
      - "Publish Glad Tidings" Act I, photostat; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie" (play) prologue, original typescript; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie" prologue, typescript copy; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie (and the Jopes)", original typescript; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie", typescript copy; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie", final typescript; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie" second version, original typescript; 1 item (Box 52)
      - "Queenie", original typescript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie", typescript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie", typescript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie" first notes, holograph; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie" notes, holograph; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie" notes, typescript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie", Fritz Kortner's and Helen Hayes' corrections and holograph manuscript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "Queenie", Fritz Kortner's corrections typescript; 1 item (Box 53)
      - "The Whisperer", original typescript; 2 items (Box 53)
      - "Young Man Axelbrod", published; 1 item (Box 53)
    - Sinclair Lewis newspaper clippings
      - Clippings about Sinclair Lewis, 4 folders, 484 items (Box 54)
      - Clippings about Sinclair Lewis, 107 items (Box 55)
      - Sinclair Lewis Scrapbook, Sauk Centre, Minnesota, 1911; 1 item (Box 55)
      - Concerning "It Can't Happen Here", 1936; Bound volume; 1 item (Box 56)
      - Concerning Dodsworth and other works, Bound volume; 1 item (Box 56)
      - Concerning the death of Sinclair Lewis, 10 Jan 1951; Bound volume; 1 item (Box 56)
  - Wells Lewis
    - Incoming correspondence
      - Concerning "They Still Say No", 40 items (Box 57)
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Wells Lewis to others, 4 items (Box 57)
      - Sinclair Lewis, 5 items (Box 57)
      - Dorothy Thompson and Sinclair Lewis, 1931-1944; undated; 55 items (Box 57)
    - Manuscripts - novel
      - "They Still Say No", pp. 1-150 holograph; 1 item (Box 57)
      - "They Still Say No", pp. 151-250 holograph; 1 item (Box 57)
      - "They Still Say No", pp. 251-350 holograph; 1 item (Box 58)
      - "They Still Say No", pp. 351-end holograph; 1 item (Box 58)
      - "They Still Say No" revisions chapter I, holograph; 1 item (Box 58)
    - Articles
      - Concerning Wells Lewis and his book, 29 items (Box 58)
  - Margaret Grierson Thompson
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Margaret Grierson Thompson (Dorothy Thompson's mother) to Margaret Thompson, undated; 1 item (Box 58)
      - Peter Thompson (Dorothy Thompson's father) to Dorothy Thompson, 21 Jun 1920; 1 item (Box 58)
  - Willard Thompson
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Willard Thompson (Dorothy Thompson's brother) to Dorothy Thompson, 07 Aug 1958-13 Sep 1960; undated; 5 items (Box 58)
  - Pamela and Bob Reeves
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Pamela Wilson (Dorothy Thompson's niece) and Bob Reeves (Pamela's husband) to Dorothy Thompson, 14 Jun 1940-29 Mar 1957; undated; 21 items (Box 58)
  - Margaret Thompson Wilson and Howard Wilson
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Margaret Thompson Wilson (Dorothy Thompson's sister) and Howard Wilson (Margaret's husband) to Dorothy Thompson, 17 Apr 1928-16 Dec 1960; undated; 89 items (Box 58)
  - Katherine Wilson
    - Outgoing correspondence
      - Katherine Wilson to Dorothy Thompson, 05 Dec 1957-11 Feb 1959; 2 items (Box 58)
- Subject files
  - Diaries, 1928-1960
    - 1928, 2 items (Box 59)
    - Sep 1927-May 1929, 1 item (Box 59)
    - 1931-1932, 1935-1936, 4 items (Box 59)
    - 1940, 1942, 3 items (Box 59)
    - 1945-1949, 6 items (Box 59)
    - 1950-1960, 6 items (Box 59)
    - Dorothy Thompson's diary, 09 Jan 1952-11 Jan 1952; 1 item (Box 60)
  - Diaries and engagement pads
    - Europe, undated; 8 items (Box 61)
    - Undated, 2 items (Box 61)
    - Address books, 9 items (Box 61)
    - Engagement pads
      - 1945-1948, 5 items (Box 61)
      - 1949-1952, 6 items (Box 61)
      - 1953-1956, 1959-1960, 9 items (Box 61)
  - Financial
    - Bank books and securities, 59 items (Box 62)
    - Bills and receipts, 3 folders, 129 items (Box 62)
    - Bank statements, 3 folders, 101 items (Box 62)
    - Checkbooks, 9 items (Box 62)
    - Estimates, 12 items (Box 63)
    - Lists, expenses, debts and assets; 3 folders, 171 items (Box 63)
    - Income tax returns, 5 items (Box 63)
    - Lists, lecture itineraries and earnings; 2 folders, 43 items (Box 63)
    - Lecture agents, miscellaneous; 84 items (Box 63)
  - Financial and legal
    - Legal papers, 4 folders, 126 items (Box 64)
    - Stebbins Pond Club records, 48 items (Box 64)
  - Photos
    - Wells Lewis, 9 items (Box 65)
    - Michael Lewis, 74 items (Box 65)
    - Sinclair Lewis, and Family; 71 items (Box 65)
    - Dorothy Thompson and Sinclair Lewis, 16 items (Box 65)
    - Dorothy Thompson, and others; 78 items (Box 65)
    - Dorothy Thompson, and others; 64 items (Box 66)
    - Dorothy Thompson, alone; 99 items (Box 66)
    - Dorothy Thompson's family, 3 items (Box 66)
  - Photos by subject
    - Joseph Bard and Dorothy Thompson, 6 items (Box 67)
    - Christmas pageant, 8 items (Box 67)
    - Dave Garroway with Dorothy Thompson, 2 items (Box 67)
    - Germany, 2 folders, 138 items (Box 67)
    - Hamburg, New York, 20 items (Box 67)
    - Home in Vermont, Plates; 2 items (Box 67)
    - Iraq, 16 items (Box 68)
    - Maxim Kopf, 14 items (Box 68)
    - Freeman Lewis, 107 items (Box 68)
    - Middle East, 2 folders, 87 items (Box 68)
    - Royalty, 17 items (Box 68)
    - Russia, 73 items (Box 68)
    - St. Vincent Millay, Edna, 34 items (Box 68)
    - "World Wide", Germany, Austria, Hungary; 97 items (Box 68)
    - Miscellaneous, 108 items (Box 68)
  - Personal miscellaneous
    - Appeal to reason, 12 items (Box 69)
    - Awards, 10 items (Box 69)
    - Family memorabilia, 22 items (Box 69)
    - Lists, business itineraries; 23 items (Box 69)
    - Lists, gifts; 19 items (Box 69)
    - Lists, people; 22 items (Box 69)
    - Lists, inventories; 31 items (Box 69)
    - Membership cards, 47 items (Box 69)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 items (Box 69)
    - Passports, 9 items (Box 69)
    - Press releases, 4 folders, 35 items (Box 70)
    - Programs and invitations, 6 items (Box 70)
    - Publications research, 6 items (Box 70)
    - Recipes, 59 items (Box 70)
    - Social unit publication, 14 items (Box 70)
    - Souvenirs and miscellaneous, 10 items (Box 70)
    - Steel, Johannes, 8 items (Box 70)
    - Teaching of reading, 15 items (Box 70)
    - United Nations, 9 items (Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous - oversized
    - Medals and awards, 7 items (Box 71)
    - Microfilm-The Philadelphia Public Ledger, 08 Jan 1922-17 Oct 1928; 1 item (Box 71)
    - Drawings, 1 of Dorothy Thompson; 2 items (Box 72)
    - Framed photos of Sinclair Lewis, 2 items (Box 72)
    - Beirut press book, 1 item (Box 72)
    - Hungarian tributes booklet, 1 item (Box 72)
    - Photographs of a Maxim Kopf painting, 1 item (Box 72)
    - The Dier Ayyub murders booklet, 1 item (Box 72)
    - The Aramco Production Training Program booklet, 1 item (Box 72)
  - Articles about Dorothy Thompson, 1914-1961
    - 1914, 1929, 1930, 1932-1935, 34 items (Box 73)
    - 1936-1937, 23 items (Box 73)
    - 1938-1939, 19 items (Box 73)
    - 1940, 2 folders, 68 items (Box 73)
    - 1941, 12 items (Box 73)
    - 1942, 69 items (Box 73)
    - 1943-1944, 28 items (Box 73)
    - 1945, 32 items (Box 73)
    - 1946, 14 items (Box 74)
    - 1947, 17 items (Box 74)
    - 1948-1949, 13 items (Box 74)
    - 1950, 24 items (Box 74)
    - 1951-1952, 30 items (Box 74)
    - 1953-1954, 12 items (Box 74)
    - 1955, 14 items (Box 74)
    - 1956-1957, 15 items (Box 74)
    - 1958, 22 items (Box 74)
    - 1959-1961, 9 items (Box 74)
    - undated, 78 items (Box 74)
  - Christmas cards-incoming and outgoing
    - Cards, 245 items (Box 75)
  - Christmas card mailing list
    - 3 X 5 Cards, 702 items (Box 76)
- Ladies Home Journal material
  - Ladies Home Journal manuscripts
    - "Across the Street, Beyond the Gate", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "American and Un-American Social Security", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "American Education Has Many Merits", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "The American Way of Life", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Are Our Children Learning the Harder or the Easier Way?", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "Are Our Teen-agers So Dumb After All?", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "Are We Developing a Robot Education?", holograph (Box 77)
    - "Are We Scaring Ourselves to Death?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Are Women Bad Employers of Other Women?", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "Are You a Candidate for a Heart Attack?", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "As Others See Us", typescript copy; 23 items (Box 77)
    - "The Baby in the Kitchen", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "The Bandit Women of Greece", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "The Banishment of Anxiety", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "The Barbarism of Divorce Laws", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Beware of Geniuses!", typescript copy; 8 items (Box 77)
    - "Can It Be a Crime to be Free?", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "Can the Cold War Be Ended?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Can Women Be Ladies?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Century in a Hurry", holograph (Box 77)
    - "The Challenge from Russia Is Not Communism", holograph (Box 77)
    - "The Challenge of Soviet Education", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Commercialism Takes-and Wears-a New Look", original typescript (Box 77)
    - "A Common Problem of High Civilization", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Community Begins at Home", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Concentration of Power is Ever a Corruptive Influence", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "The Crisis in American Education", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "A Critic Looks at Our Foreign Policy", typescript copy; 25 items (Box 77)
    - "Dandelions for Father?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Defense and the Public Schools", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Democracy in Theory and Practice", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Depression and War", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Desert Christmas", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Destruction and Mind", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "A Dimension of Travel is Time", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "The Discrepancy Between Democratic Ideals and Realities", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Divorces Are Not Crimes; They Are Tragedies", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Do American Educators Know What They Are Up To?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Do Our Schools Need an S.O.S.?", typescript copy (Box 77)
    - "Do We Misunderstand Romantic Love?", typescript copy; 18 items (Box 77)
    - "The Education of the Emotions Is Primary", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The 'Educators' Need Re-education", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Employed Woman and Her Household", typescript copy; 5 items (Box 78)
    - "The Farm Problem and Me", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "For a Sober But Happy New Year", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "For the First Time in Man's History", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "A Foreign Policy for All Americans", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Freedom, To Survive, Must Be Self-Limited", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "From Whom All Blessings Flow", typescript copy; 11 items (Box 78)
    - "The Great Affirmative", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Great Confrontation", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "How to Preserve Civilization", typescript copy; 2 items (Box 78)
    - "If I Had a Daughter", original typescript (Box 78)
    - "If No One Else-We, the Mothers", original typescript (Box 78)
    - "I Like Americans", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "I'm the Child of a King", holograph (Box 78)
    - "I Remember Me", typescript copy (Box 3)
    - "Is American Youth Radical?", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Is Johnny a Clinical Case?", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Is Morality 'Normal'?", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Is There a Climate of Fear in America?", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Is There a Right to 'Bad Taste'?", original typescript (Box 78)
    - "It's All the Fault of the Women!", holograph (Box 78)
    - "I've Stopped Throwing Some of My Weight Around", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "I Write of Russian Women", typescript copy; 31 items (Box 78)
    - "The Key to Freedom", typescript copy; 2 items (Box 78)
    - "The Lady Can be Vengeful", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Lesson of Korea", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Liberty and Conformity in America", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Limits of Public School Education", original typescript (Box 78)
    - "The Little Towns", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Loneliest Man in the White House", holograph; 12 items (Box 78)
    - "The Mar Wind Doth Blow", holograph (Box 78)
    - "Medical Care and Its Discontents", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Moments That Educate", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "A Moral Equivalent for War", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "Moral Laxity Results from Moral Disillusionments" (Box 78)
    - "The Most Beautiful Form of Courage", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "The Most Powerful Anti-poison", typescript copy (Box 78)
    - "My Husband, Maxim Kopf", original typescript (Box 78)
    - "Must Schools Be Palaces?", typescript copy; 23 items (Box 78)
    - "National Defense Cannot Be Intermittent", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Necessity and Function of An Opposition", holograph (Box 79)
    - "The Neglected Art and Science", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The New Mr. Casper Milquetoasts", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "A Not Fantastic Dream", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "Now We All Thank Our God", holograph; 11 items (Box 79)
    - "Oh, Professor!", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Old Bible and the New", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "On Living Dangerously", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "On Loyalty", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Only the Rose", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Our Fear-ridden Middle Classes", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Our Remarkable Presidency", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "Out of This World", original typescript; 11 items (Box 79)
    - "Palaces Empty of Education", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "The Paradox of Evil and Good", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The People's Tribunal", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "A Primer on the Cold War", typescript copy; 9 items (Box 79)
    - "Queer People", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "A Question of Value", original typescript; 4 items (Box 79)
    - "Race Suicide of the Intelligent", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Radioactivity Threatens Future Generations", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Ragged Beggar Stands Again", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "A Reason to Live and a Reason to Die", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Remarkable Inefficiency of Efficiency", holograph (Box 79)
    - "Report on the American Communist", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Respect for the Law Begins at Home", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Revolution in Mothballs", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Right to Happiness", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "Road Accidents Can be Cut Down", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Romantic Love is Exaggerated", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Russian Poet-Prophets", typescript copy; 20 items (Box 79)
    - "The Salem That Never Burned Witches", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Satan Versus Beelzebub", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Secret of Survival", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Sophisticates are Not the Wise", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Soviet School Child", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Speaking of Operations -", original typescript; 12 items (Box 79)
    - "Technology Does Not Lead to Collectivism", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "There is a Time", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "There Was a Child Went Forth", typescript copy; 6 items (Box 79)
    - "United Nations: Shadow and Substance", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "The Untilled Acre", original typescript; 4 items (Box 79)
    - "War and Revolution", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Was Hitler Really Crazy", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "We Can Conquer Minds and Hearts", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "Western Civilization Needs More Air and Room", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "What About the Twenty-first Century?", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "What is a World Citizen", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "What is Wrong with American Women?", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "What Price Liberty?", typescript copy (Box 79)
    - "What the World Most Needs", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "Where is My President?", holograph (Box 79)
    - "Which Way Today's Youth?", original typescript (Box 79)
    - "The White Sofa", typescript copy; 24 items (Box 79)
    - "Who are the Aged?, holograph (Box 80)
    - "Why and What Should Johnny Read?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Why Can't Americans Sleep?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Why Don't We Take More Time to Live?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Why Russia and the West Must Not Go to War", original typescript (Box 80)
    - "Why Should Superior Men Run for Public Office?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Will America Become 'Masses' or Stay 'People'?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Will the Masses be Subdued by an Elite of Public Guardians?", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "Woman", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "The Woman's Revolution in the Arab World", typescript copy (Box 80)
    - "The World of Grandma Moses", typescript copy; 22 items (Box 80)
    - Untitled articles, 4 items (Box 80)
  - Ladies Home Journal published articles
    - 1937-1938, 30 items (Box 80)
    - 1939-1941, 44 items (Box 80)
    - 1941-1943, 42 items (Box 80)
    - 1944-1946, 32 items (Box 80)
    - 1947-1949, 40 items (Box 80)
    - 1950-1952, 36 items (Box 81)
    - 1953-1955, 35 items (Box 81)
    - 1956-1958, 38 items (Box 81)
    - 1959-1960, 33 items (Box 81)
    - Undated, 2 items (Box 82)
    - Suggestions for articles, 20 items (Box 82)
  - Ladies Home Journal fan mail
    - Education
      - 1943, 1944, 1952, 1953, 8 items (Box 82)
      - 1954-1955, 45 items (Box 82)
      - 1956, 127 items (Box 82)
      - 1957, 29 items (Box 82)
      - 1958, 51 items (Box 82)
      - 1959, 74 items (Box 83)
      - 1960, 120 items (Box 83)
      - Undated, 33 items (Box 83)
  - Ladies Home Journal fan mail on specific articles
    - "Discrepancy Between Democratic Ideals and Relations", 20 items (Box 83)
    - "Do Women Make Bad Employers?", 9 items (Box 83)
    - "I Am the Child of a King", 206 items (Box 83)
    - "Is America's Moral Code Breaking Down?", 21 items (Box 84)
    - "It's All the Fault of Women", 11 items (Box 84)
    - "Let Me Tell You About My Heart Attack", 18 items (Box 84)
    - "My Husband, Maxim Kopf", 119 items (Box 84)
    - "Meaning for Us All", 51 items (Box 84)
    - "Medical Care and Its Discontents", 19 items (Box 84)
    - "Our Remarkable Presidency", 11 items (Box 84)
    - "A Question of Value", 101 items (Box 84)
    - "The Remarkable Inefficiency of Efficiency, 2 items (Box 84)
    - Articles about Russia, 37 items (Box 84)
    - "Where Is My President?", 27 items (Box 84)
    - "Who Are the Aged?", 12 items (Box 84)
  - Ladies Home Journal on general subjects
    - General fan mail, 1956-1957; 12 items (Box 84)
    - General fan mail, 1958; 3 folders, 244 items (Box 85)
    - General fan mail, 1959; 2 folders, 100 items (Box 86)
    - General fan mail, Jan 1960-Aug 1960; 51 items (Box 86)
    - General fan mail, Sep 1960-Oct 1960; 51 items (Box 86)
    - General fan mail, 1960; 67 items (Box 87)
    - General fan mail, 1961; 13 items (Box 87)
    - "Crank" letters, 11 items (Box 87)
    - Undated, 25 items (Box 87)
- "On the Record" articles
  - Typescripts
    - "On the Record" typescripts, 1940-1948; 19 items (Box 88)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Apr 1949; 25 items (Box 88)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, May-Jul 1949; 39 items (Box 88)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Aug 1949-Jan 1950; 47 items (Box 88)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Feb-Jul 1950; 46 items (Box 89)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Aug-Oct 1950; 39 items (Box 89)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Nov 1950-Apr 1951; 40 items (Box 89)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, May 1951-Oct 1951; 58 items (Box 89)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Nov 1951-Jan 1952; 40 items (Box 90)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Feb 1952-Apr 1952; 37 items (Box 90)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, May-Jul 1952; 42 items (Box 90)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Aug-Dec 1952; 65 items (Box 90)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1953; 37 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-Jun 1953; 39 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jul-Sep 1953; 35 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Oct-Dec 1953; 39 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1954; 38 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-Jun 1954; 38 items (Box 91)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jul-Sep 1954; 33 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Oct-Dec 1954; 41 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1955; 36 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-Jun 1955; 39 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jul-Sep 1955; 40 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Oct-Dec 1955; 34 items (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1956 (Box 92)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-Jun 1956; 40 items (Box 93)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jul-Sep 1956; 38 items (Box 93)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Oct-Dec 1956; 39 items (Box 93)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1957; 41 items (Box 93)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-Jun 1957; 40 items (Box 93)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jul-Sep 1957; 39 items (Box 94)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Oct-Dec 1957; 39 items (Box 94)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jan-Mar 1958; 39 items (Box 94)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Apr-May 1958; 26 items (Box 94)
    - "On the Record" typescripts, Jun-Aug 1958; 31 items (Box 94)
    - "America as a Successor of Empires", undated; typescript copy (Box 95)
    - "America is Losing for a Reason", undated; typescript copy (Box 95)
    - "The Arabs of Israel", undated; typescript copy (Box 95)